嘿，这里是Mr.B，今天我们要买下
hey! MrBeast's here. Today we're gonna buy
这家食品超市里的所有商品，开始吧
every item in this store, let's do it
我觉得光凭你一人完成不了
I don't think you can do this all by yourself
我觉得你应该闭嘴
I don't think you should speak anymore
我也觉得我该闭嘴了
I don't think I should either
这个视频的要点基本上就是要
So you get the gist of the video, we're basically
买下这家店里所有商品
buying literally everything in the store,
但如果只有克里斯（Chris），我，还有
which if it was just Chris, me, and
钱德勒（Chandler）估计会耗时一辈子，所以我带了一些朋友
Chandler would take forever, so I brought some friends
确保你拿了所有的商品，不要留下一丁点东西在货架！
Make sure you get everything, don't leave a single thing on the shelf!
看看这周围的人，我把
Look at all these people here, I just like
我通讯录名单都联系了一遍
literally went down my contact list
我说，嘿，能过来帮我搬空一座食品商店吗？
I was like, hey, you want to help me buy everything in the store?
然后令人惊喜的是每个人都说，没问题！
and surprisingly everyone was just like, sure!
放进去一些薄荷糖
Here's some mint thins
这里，我们来帮康纳（Conor Phillip）填满手推车
Here, let's, let's help Conor Phillip full his cart
-你要一些萝卜罐头吗？ -好啊 -给你，玩的开心
-Here, you want some carrots? -Sure -There you go, have fine
老铁，这里有各式各样的果汁
Oh man, we got all kinds of juices over here
-让我来帮你 -谢了，吉米（唐纳森）！
-Let me help you -Thanks!! Jimmy (Donaldson)
好的，你的手推车已经满了，拿着这个信用卡去付款吧
Alright, your cart is full, take this credit card and go pay for it
这些能给我吗？他们是我的最爱
These are my favorite, can I have them?
可以，给你个手推车，你放进去啥我们都会给它买单
Yes, I got you a cart, whatever you put in there we will pay for
-好的 -玩的开心。给，来点腌黄瓜
-Ok! -Have fine. Here, grab some pickles
嘿，这是我第二次排队了
Hey, this is my second time in the line
大哥，你都拿了什么？
What did you get, sir？
所有我能自己拿的东西
Everything I can get my hands on
-给你卡，去结账吧 -爽歪歪
-Here you go, go checkout. okay, alright, here's a credit card -Awesome
你可能想知道为什么我们要买所有的这些东西？
You might be wondering why are we buying all this stuff?
我们买它是因为我们想把它捐给
What we're buying it because we
慈善机构，比如食物银行（赈济处），
want to give it to charity, like a food bank,
流浪庇护所，或一个随机的路人，
a homeless shelter, or if a random
他想吃豆子，我们就给他
guy on the street who wants beans, we'll just give it to him
你知道他们为你做了一款豆子吗？ 《有钱有内涵》
Did you know that made beans about you?
德斯汀（Destin），你都拿啥了？
Destin, what do you have right now?
-大玉米罐头 -所有的这些！有打火机吗？
-Big corn guy -All of this corn. Do you have a lighter?
-打火机？ -恩
-A lighter? -Yeah
你要打火机干嘛？
Why are you need a lighter for?
给你做爆米花啊！
So you can make popcorn
德斯汀，我都看不到你了
I can't even see you anymore, Destin
是吗？
Oh, really?
所以还需要更多商品
So they need  more stuff and
还需要付款 -是真的顾客吗？
they needs to be paid for -There's  a real customer?
真实的顾客
A real customer
你不想买点其他的吗？
You don't want anything else?
你买吧，我们会付钱的
We will pay for it
我们要把整个超市都买完
We're gonna buy everything in the store. So..
看到你想要的，只管拿就行
Anything you want, just grab it
芝士泡芙，走吧我们去找
We need cheese puffs, let's go find it
我们现在需要芝士泡芙！
We need some cheese puffs right now!
找到了，有人给她了
She got the cheese puffs, he gave her cheese puffs
-很好 -我们没事了
-Ok -We're good we're good
有人照顾好她了
She's taking care of
克里斯（Chris） 很擅长一件事，就是泡芙和猪油
There is one thing Chris is good for, it is cheese puffs and lard
-我拿了桶猪油。我很不高兴 -为啥？
-I got our tub of lard. I'm upset -Why?
有人在藏奇多，以备日后吃
He's hiding those Cheetos for later
这都不是我们的商店，但我们全面接手了
This isn't even our store, we have like a full-scale operation
这些人都是我的员工
All these people I'm paying to do this
-他在干什么？他哪找的那个车子？ -我木知啊
-What is he doing? Where did he get that? -I don't know
我弄了一堆土豆，一罐豆子
I got a lot of potatos, one can of beans
到目前我们花多少钱了？
How much have we spent so far?
才花了$800美元，伙计们你们都在干嘛？？？
We're only up to $800 guys!! What are you doing??
-来搬点卫生纸 -所有的？ -是的，好吧
-Let's do toilet paper -All of it? -Yes, well
这效率也太低，一个稍大点的卫生纸就填满了整个购物车
that was not efficient, one bigger toilet paper fill up the entire card
伯特（Bert），你想要宇宙布朗？
Bert oh, you want some cosmic brownies?
是的，都在找自己想吃的呗
Yeah, I'm doing my part
别再扔我吃的！每次都这样！！
Don't throw them again! every time!!
-你手推车还是空的 -不是空的，我有宇宙布朗尼
-Your car's empty -No, it's not, I got cosmic brownies
我能来点...反正都要全买了
Can I just like, I mean it's probably like buying everything
我要努力吃布朗尼蛋糕，要健康!!
I'm trying to be healthy to eating brownies
我们有难题了，
We are having a little bit of a dilemma,
我们已经填满了每辆购物车，现在怎么办？
we filled up every card. Now what?
你身后是什么玩意？
What is happening behind you?
发生了什么？
What is going on?
请让一让！
Excuse us!
我们不想妨碍你们
We don't want to interrupt this
给你一点，以防你突然也想吃一点
Here you go, just in case you want some
谢谢小钱钱！
Thank you!
-那是什么鬼东西？ -我木知啊
-What was that? -I don't know
你们真的在吃麦片吗？就在我们做了
How are you, are you guys really eating cereal after the
上期视频之后
last video we did
是啊！
Yep!
上个视频里我们给了一个流浪庇护所价值$10万美元的物品
In the past we did a video where we gave $100,000 worth of stuff to a homeless shelter
但是比较杂乱，不容易拆开，
and it was really unorganized and hard to unpack and
也不容易存放，所以现在我们
hard to like put away for them. So now we're
把所有物品放在像这样的，类似糖果盒的盒子里，
putting everything in boxes, like this is a candy box,
因此对于食物银行更容易
so it's easier for the food bank
将所有补充物分类和存储起来
they would take all this supplies to to like sort it and store
朋友们，来点订阅，因为这可能花我一大笔钱
Can you guys subscribe! This is probably gonna cost me a lot of money
你看看他们打包了多少商品
I mean look at how much stuff they are arriving
我们就是随便把东西堆在手推车里，
Like we just literally been putting stuff in carts
我都不知道有什么。但是，
and I have no idea what it's been. But,
我知道我们有猪油，并且我很高兴
I do know that we've got some lard and I'm very happy about it
我们在买的时候他们也在运送更多的货物
They're delivering more food as we're buying it
我去，真的吗？
Wait, really?
来了一辆送货车
They poured the truck backed in
我们不需要了，别送了，走开.. 我们花了太多钱了
We don't need it, we don't need it! go away.. We're spending too much money
我需要观众姥爷们去ShopMrBeast买些衣裳
I need you guys to go shopMrBeast.com buy some merch
因为我没想到竟然还有送货？？快去买吧亲
Because I was not expecting another delivery, sooo yeah
这个是我的锅
Alright, that was my fault
钱德勒，玩的还好吗？很好，也就只有这些了
Chandler，are you having fun? good, that's all you have it
小杰杰，我真为你骄傲！
Jerry, I'm proud of you!
花我的钱，这就是我想要的
Spending my money, this is what I want
-谢谢 -不足挂齿
-Thanks -You are welcome
这就是我想要的，空货架
This is what I want! Empty show
当我们说要买所有东西，就指我们需要所有东西
When we say we are buying everything, we need everything
除了一些香蕉
Except for maybe some bananas
我们将近花了$14278.01
We are up to fourteen thousand two hundred
$14279.03美元
and seventy-eight to seventy-nine
很好，这个收银台还阔以
Alright, this one is doing good
好，这个显示器有
and on this register left is six
$6261.70美元
thousand two hundred and sixty one dollars
到目前为止，我们花了大约$2万3千块
So far we spent about twenty-three thousand dollars
-我们的目标不是要花$10万美元吗？ -是的
-Aren't we supposed to spend like a hundred -Yeah
所以我们相当于完成了百分之23
So we're like twenty-three percent done
-差不多 -很好，待会见
-Basically -All right, I'll see you later
钱德勒讨厌腌黄瓜，所以唯一合理的事情就是
Chandler hates pickles, so the only logical thing
来一辆装满腌黄瓜的手推车给钱德勒
to do is to fill this cart with pickles and give to him
-小钱钱去哪了？ -钱德勒？
-Where is chan chan? -Chandler?
-小钱钱跑哪去了？
-Where is chan Chandler?
中间来一段钱德勒拉屎的视频
Leave it to Chandler to be pooping in the middle of vedio
小钱钱，我们有一个惊喜要给你
Chandler, all right we got a surprise for you
大概一年前
Like, a year ago
-哦，好吧，知道就行 -耶，这条过道基本快要空了
-Oh, okay, good -Yeah we're almost done with this aisle
大概还有五个过道吧
We sort of like five more
没事
It's all right
-大概20％ -这太多了，太多了，好样的
-It's 20% -Yeah that's a lot that's a lot, good job
这里需要警示，我马上回来
I need cuidado, I'll be right back
安全第一！！
Safety first
我单纯觉得你们不能堆太高
I feel like you guys shouldn't be boxing in the employees
牛掰
Yes
我有番茄汁，我们有番茄酱
We got tomato sauce, we got tomato paste,
我们有番茄丁
we got diced tomatoes
哦，你叫它们西红柿
Oh, you call them tomatoes
好吧，我想我们不能一起出去浪了
well I guess we can't hang out then
天呐，看看这些手推车
Oh, my God. Look at all these carts
-世界末日的征兆, 什么鬼？ -我们买的比我想象要多
-Checking the apocalypse. What? -We bought more than I thought we bought
里面就像个正在全面开展的的军事行动
I mean this is like a full-scale military operation we got going on yet
好消息我们还要继续
Good thing that we have more
目前为止我们花了2万5千美元，那边那个
So far we spent twenty five thousand and on that one over there
我们花了8千
we've spent eight thousand
当'省太多'之城陷落时你们在哪里
Where were you guys when the siege of save-a-lot went down
为什么不来救援？
Why did you not come to the rescue?
为啥怼的是我？
Why me?
所以是的，我们从字面上扫空了整个个个个
So yeah, we literally cleared this entireeee
钱德勒，我们打算清扫整个过道
Chandler! We're trying to clear all the aisles
起来，别在上面睡觉！
Get, stop sleeping on them
我不能说我买光了所有的东西，但如果还有一个钱德勒要出售的话
I can't say I bought everything in the store if there's a Chandler for sale
好了
There we go
现在我们清理了整个货面
Now we've cleared all this roof
-给我拍拍背 -交给我了
-You wanna wipe my back -I got you
现在进展的越来越快，所以我们
So things were moving fast enough, so we
只能在大街上雇一些随机的路人
actually ended up just hiring random people off the street
到了现在这个点，我不知道我要给多少人薪水，
So at this point I don't even know how many people I'm paying for an hour
可能25个人
probably like 25
不清楚，但确实有很多人在工作
I don't know, but we have a lot of people working
嘿！你有什么发现？你弄了松饼？
Hey! What you got there? you got Twinkies?
好吧，听着，如果你不告诉别人的话
All right look, I'll give you
我分你一个
guys one if you don't tell anybody
-这有必要吗？-超过$1万了，很好！！
-Was that necessary? -We are over ten grand? Perfect!
不客气怎么说？ 得哒塔，阿里嘎多！
How do I say you are welcome, de nada arigato
那是日本话
That's Japanese
谢谢好心人， Mr.B
thank you Mr. beast
谢谢好人， Mr.B
Thank You Mr. beast
今天是你的幸运日，这些全部免费
It's your lucky day, this is all free
谢谢Mr. B，谢谢！
Thank You, Thank You!
Mr. B，太感谢了
Mr. beast, thank you so much
来自'省太多'食物超市的感谢
shout out for save-a-lot. Thank you so much
生意突然爆裂！
business is booming
看看我们买了多少东西？我们花了多少钱？
Look how much stuff we're buy? How much money have we spent ?
-我木知啊 -我应该知道的！
-I don't know -I should probably know！
去ShopMrBeast买点商品成为
shopMrBeast.com become an investor
慈善的投资人，我也可以多做点这样的事，并给我的摄像小哥发工资
by buying merch. I  can do stuff like this and pay my cameraman
他想要一个东西，想要问问你
He just wants one thing, he wants to ask you
不，不不，别就来一个啊，来一百多件，
Oh, no no no, don't buy one thing, but like a hundred things
-不管你买什么都会付钱的 -好吧
-Whatever you buy we will pay for -Okay
你能行的
You got this
嘿，达斯汀，多搬点薯片
Hey hey Dustin, we need you to get more chips man
-我懂 -你懂了
-I got it -You got it
嘿，泰勒，我是说我们需要更多的番茄酱
Hey, Taylor, I mean we need to get more ketchup
我估计其他的就剩下在树上的了
I think they're at ketchup tree
看呐，这说的是你，大号处男
Hey look, that's you, extra virgin
兄弟，这看起来很美好，还需要很长时间
Dude, that looks beautiful! It's gonna take forever
还是要花点时间看看
Still take a while
看看你帮忙的下场？你弄掉所有东西
See what happens when you help? You drop everything
-好吧，因为盒子坏了 -是嘛
-Well the box was broken -Aha
-好的，我们来漫步一下
-Alright, let's go for a little stroll
如你所见，货架已空
As you can see, empty
-三号过道，如你所见，这是啥？克瑞斯 -啥都没有
-Aisle number three, as you can see, what is it? Chris -Empty
四号走道，基本空了
This is Aisle number four, it's almost empty
五号走道，也快空了
In Aisle numer five, almost empty
还剩下一点汽水饮料，还在处理中
Got a little bit of soda left we're still working on it
恩.. 这看上去真的很紧绷，跟个炸弹一样
This is uh, this is really tight, that's like a bomb
你能打开吗？
You want open it?
别他喵的指着我啊？你为啥指着我，吉米？
Don't! Why do you pointing at me? why do you pointing at me? Jimmy!
小钱钱，我给你$100块要是你打开的话
Oh, Chandler, I will give you a hundred dollars if you open it
$100块
a hundred dollars
好，可以了，可以，小心摄像机
Alright! stop stop, the camera
他得到$100美元
He gets a hundred dollars
注意！打扫一下5号走道
Attention! clean up on aisle 5
钱德勒洒了些汽水，沙雕行为，谢谢
Chandler spilled some soda, this is dumb, thank you
-你做的很好 -我能来个簸箕吗？
-U are doing a great job -Can I get a dustpan?
-你这样清理不对！ -咋了？
-That's not how you clean it up. Chandler -What?
-那是液体 -这是个扫帚，不是液体
-That's the liquid -This is a broom, not the liquid
大沙雕
Stupid
-四个小时
-For four hours
四个小时！
Four hours!
五分钟，嘣蹦蹦
5 boo boo boom
我有点虚，害怕看到截至到现在花多少了，
I'm scared to see how much we spent. It's
差不多两个小时没看收银台了
been like two hours since I checked cash register
这些是最后一批不易腐烂的食物
These are the last non-perishable items
因为食品收纳所不喜欢有易腐烂的食物存储
because the food shelter don't want perishable thing in the entire store
-最近怎么样？ -很好，很好，大伙还好吗？
-How are you doing! -Fine, fine, how-how is everybody?
大伙还行，你看上状态不错
Great oH, you look good
我们刚搬空了整座超市
We just got this whole store
这个过道已经空了
This aisle is empty
克里斯，这个过道有什么？ -有空气
-Chris. What is this aisle? -It is empty
哇，这里原先是摆满物品的
Wow, this was full of stuff, oh my goodness
-这个过道也是空的 -你的银行卡也是！ ！
-And this aisle is empty too -And so is your bank account!
扎心又真实，好的，我们出发派送食物到流浪庇护所吧
Sadly yes, alright let's go give it all to a homeless shelter
走
Let's do it
虽然花了很长时间，但我们最终付清了全部账单
So it took quite a while but we ended up paying the full bill
大概7万美金
it was like $70,000,
这些再加上我们临时工的薪水
we got it all covered plus whatever we spent on the other people
最终我们还是花了一大堆钱
so we ended up spending quite a bit
她要打印收据了
She's about to print the receipt
绝对会很有趣
This is gonna be interesting
价值$7万美元的杂货
Seventy thousand dollars worth groceries
来一个领带
They made me a tie
$7万美金，这是我一生中见过的最昂贵的时刻
$70,000, this is the most expensive time I ever seen in my life
疯了，你喜欢吗？
That is insane, you like it?
你们都应该试试，只需要花费$7万美金，还可以得到
You guys should try this, just go spin 70 grand and
一个收据领带，快看那个收据有多长，
you can have a receipt-tie. Look how big that is,
大概有20英尺，$7万美金的杂货收据
that'sprobably like a 20-foot receipt, $70000 dollars
我们在食物银行，然后我们要给他们食物
Alright, we're at a food bank and we're gonna give them food
哇，这真是堆起来了，吉米
Wow this is stacking up. Jimmy
是啊，就像学校贷款，和美国
It is, like college debt and America.
德尔塔C9军事行动按计划进行中
Military operation deltas c9 is going according to plan
-哦，瞧瞧这个 -喔，这些，这些是我的！！
-Oh look at this -Oh ho woow, these are these are mine
维京人好这口，好的，懂了
Oh Vikings like, okay alright
哦，这个已经打开了，你懂的
Alright, this one already open, that's you already know that means
小钱钱，你丫在干嘛？
Chandler. What are you doing?
我们得喂饱每个人是吧！！ 嘿，我很好，但我觉得
We got to feed everybody! hey, I'm good I think
那边有个人需要点吃的
there's somebody over there they needs
-我马上回来 -他刚是拿了蜂蜜面包是吗？
-I'll be right back -Did he just take the honey buns?
我想他刚刚拿了一堆蜂蜜小面包跑了
I think he just took a bunch of honey buns
钱德勒，这是给无家可归的人准备的。还回来！！
Chandler, those for homeless people. Give it back
-我能有一个吗？ -不行！
-Can I have one? -No
甜蜜面包侠
Honey-bun man
这刚从他的口袋掉出来
This just fell out of his pocket
别什么？
Not what?
好的，好奇里面装了些什么？谁能想到呢！！
Alright, I wonder how full this.. Who would have thought?
更多食物，更多箱子，哇~
More food and more boxes Wow
好的，这就是我们的全部
All right, so this is all the stuff we had in the emos
我想观众们比较好奇这些食物的去向
I guess people are probably curious what is it gonna go towards
好的，我们每周服务1,000至1,500人
well, we serve anywhere from 1,000 to 1,500 people a week
我很惊讶我们能把所有的东西都放进去
I'm surprised we could fit all that stuff we did in there
所以他最终会交给需要它的人们（鼓掌）
So it's going to people that need it
-是的，对他们来说很重要 -好，好的，我也很感谢，
-They really need it  -Yeah yeah I appreciate it, thanks
谢谢你允许我们帮助别人
for allowing us to help people yeah
好了，伙计们，这个视频真的很贵
Alright guys, this video was actually really expensive
我需要你去买点商品
I need you to go invest and merch
因为你不买一些商品
because of you don't buy merch
我在未来也就做不起这样的事情
I just can't afford to do stuff like this in the future
看这个野兽磨砂连帽衫和这个办公室连帽衫，他们真的很帅气！
See this frosted beast hoodie and this office hoodie, they are sexy
这个叫mymerch的公司，
This company that I didn't makeup named mymerch
连续三年评为YouTube最帅气连帽衫。
The sexiest YouTube merch three years in a row
巧合吗？我不觉得
Coincidence? I think not
来ShopMrBeast买点商品
at the shopMrBeast.com buy a bunch of stuff,
让我有能力在未来继续做这种慈善的活动
so I can afford to keep doing things like this in the future
爱你们
Love you guys
现在你们知道了，各位，我们买的每一件东西都将用于帮助低收入家庭，
And there you have it, folks, every single thing we bought will go to help
或者一些单纯需要帮助的人，
low-income families or just people who need it in general,
所以我真的很高兴做了这些
so I'm really happy about that
哦，对了，我们当时也买了很多杂货给顾客
oh yeah and we also bought a lot of people's groceries at the store
这个我倒是忘了
I did forget about that
无所谓，希望你们喜欢，我也喜欢做这样的视频
Anyways I hope you guys enjoyed and I like making videos like this
希望你能有一个美好的一天
and hope you have a good day
我们现在在动物收容所，在这里
We're at the Animal Shelter, where we're
捐赠我们最后来自'省太多'超市的食品
donating the last of the stuff that we got from uh save-a-lot
是一些狗食啊，猫食啊之类的东西
This is all the dog food and the cat food and stuff that
我们不能给那些无家可归的人
we got and we can't give it to homeless people
这些所有的食物都去哪里了
So where does all the food go to
我们每年收容大约3千只动物,
We process about 3,000 animals a year through the shelter and dogs and cats,
这些食物会支持所有的狗狗进入我们的护理
so it supports all the dogs that come into our care
太酷了，很高兴我们能帮忙
That's awesome, well I'm glad we can help you
谢谢你们
Thank you so much for sure
谢谢，Mr. beast
Thank You Mr. beast